<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Stormlab</title><link href="https://stormlab.eu/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://stormlab.eu/feeds/tag_brent-weeks.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://stormlab.eu/</id><updated>2015-08-25T00:00:00+02:00</updated><entry><title>The Night Angel Trilogy</title><link href="https://stormlab.eu/the-night-angel-trilogy.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-08-25T00:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Julfur</name></author><id>tag:stormlab.eu,2015-08-25:the-night-angel-trilogy.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style="float: right;" src="https://pics-librarything.r.worldssl.net/picsizes/ae/0e/ae0e5ddf878015f597830636241444341587343.jpg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really enjoy reading, especially Fantasy. I'm just writing down what books I've enjoyed and why without spoiling too much.
This is the last trigoly I've read : The Night Angel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wasn't sure what it was about but that was a pleasant surprise. I was a bit short on books in my Kindle on my way home so I took the bet. 
It was rough, dark, but at the same time a bit childish mostly because of some characters attitude.
Full of action, violence and deceptive romance.. the ending wasn't to my taste but that's just me.
My first time reading books from Brent Weeks, maybe I'll try the second trilogy he is working on (Lightbringer series).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, if you're into plop twist, immortals, magic, assassins, depravity, sexual tension, a bit of gore on the side.. this trilogy is for you. Once you start you just want to keep reading, the story is unfolding slowly and you keep wondering what the heck is going on.. The author likes to drop massive bombs (aka plop twist) that almost always hit home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Night Angel Trilogy:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Way of Shadows (2008)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shadow's Edge (2008)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beyond the Shadows (2008)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I'm french and might look for those books in the future, I'll keep the french name of those books in this article (yes I'm lazy):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;La Voie des ombres, Bragelonne (2009) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Le Choix des ombres, Bragelonne  (2009) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Au-delà des ombres, Bragelonne (2009) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brent_Weeks"&gt;Brent Weeks Wikipedia page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="Brent Weeks"></category><category term="The Night Angel Trilogy"></category></entry></feed>